Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the f-
We are Kangol
Hi, Alex has gotten. Hey, what's up?
What's up?
Sorry, I was just talking and I was not even on the on the stage. I was trying to explain. Yeah
I'll open the I'll open the panel for an hour as a courtesy to Teresa
Also, I want to perform the other two the other two readings for the chat and then I will re
Reopen a response, but I bet guys check out the screen. I did as her link right there shit
There's an easier way to do it. Can you post your link in the chat to Teresa?
Because I want everyone to subscribe to her make sure you subscribe to
traveling gypsy tarot
Okay, yeah, thank you friend. Thank you for thank you Teresa for sponsoring this panel tonight. Yeah, thank you Teresa. Thank you very much
So what's up
Man, I had a crazy as night
You're a crazy night. What happens I?
Made I had went to go out some drinks, and then I met this sex. He has
woman girl
And it was really weird, but I mean, we hit it perfectly, but then as they were close
in the bar, then these people come up to us and really, hey, you guys want to go party?
And I was ready for how they are, fuck it.
So we went and they wanted to play beer pong and blah, blah, blah, and they gave us all
these drinks.
And like.
That was it like I was like what what the fuck will they pick us but it was until like 7 a.m. This morning
And I honestly I'm still drunk from last night
Hey, it was fun. It was a lot of fun. I like this girl
Tomorrow I'm gonna take her to the museum and do some fancy
Yeah, oh yeah, and people in the chat you didn't hear me say because I was I was off-camera at the time for right now
But I was I did say I would open for an hour
in our
And I and go back to this channel, so I'm keeping all my promises is okay, so so you're running a professional business here
I know I'm just like people are people like psyched to like to pick on everything. It's like like every little thing
It's like geez
It's like I thought I was talking like everything and like making that clear, but it was like I was off camera
Well, I mean
I'm just gonna hold that because I enjoy your company a lot. They I think you're you're my gay friend
You're like now I can say I have a gay friend, which is you
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're my good friend, but yeah, but that's it. I'm just gonna I
Respect I respect your professionalism and your work ethic
Yeah, I do
Look at you smoking weed. Yes
The name is but no, I'm opening the panel for an hour Teresa for you. Yeah
Yeah, you created that you you fucking birthed me
Sponding yeah, or or more like, you know, if you were to come up Teresa
That's me. So you were actually you got clipped a few times road. No, man. You got clipped, right?
Really? Yeah. Well, I clipped you on mine because the looks more your earlier
The Big Misha, yeah, I think I think I'm creating I'm working on a new one. Her name is gonna be well Tonya Perkins
Latonya Perkins now while Tonya like
WALT that while Tonya Perkins
What do you think of that name you think that's a good name
It's a great game. Well, Tony had Perkins. Yeah, that way like it was funny when they
when people when new people come into chat right and then there's well Tony and they don't know
like it's an inside joke because that's what I like the other inside joke like for everybody to
laugh. Is it like an inside joke like is there a further joke other than just like it's a funny
like black sounding it sounds like there's like a further inside joke there that I'm not in on.
No, I think I mean it you are we're all in the same
Like I'm just saying that while Tony Perkins. That's pretty funny and she's gonna be really yeah well Tony and maybe
She's gonna be really nice and she's gonna love everybody
But like when new people come in the chat, they'll actually think that while Tony Perkins like a real human
I mean, I would I mean, you know big Nisha full of me. I know
You know, I actually thought for like months. He said the big nation
And then you actually made her a mod why'd you why'd you like you actually had mod of moderation privileges there? Why'd you give up?
What would you tell me I had a mod her and then you had to kill her off
Do you think that like like I take that seriously?
I think it ends there
Oh, gosh, okay
Look at by my other glasses. Okay
Like
No, Big Misha was just there like an inside joke and she was she was nice to everybody
She was I mean, I liked her I liked her a lot
I mean, I really do miss her like she was such a pleasure to having the fact I was thinking maybe like bring zombie
Nisha, you know how she died and then use like zombie Nisha like she's back from the dead. Oh
Yeah, like a ghost Nisha. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah zombie Nisha. What do you think?
zombie Nisha
That'd be a cute name is on Venetia. That sounds like a good name, too
Oh, it's on Venetia and well Tonya Perkins
But what I think well Tonya because I want to create a whole new character is like, you know
The people do the Dungeons and Dragons thing. This is my this is my Dungeons and Dragons thing
I just create characters. So while Tonya Perkins, maybe she's from Barbados
Or maybe yeah, and then she want to make the fucking rum punch for everybody is a yeah
You want that rum punch boy?
Have you ever been to Barbados I have not I've not been to the Caribbean I don't believe I've been to events
I'm not in Florida. I've been to South Carolina for the south. I've been I think
Barbados is awesome. Good night by traveling to see thank you so much for sponsoring. I love you. You've a great day
Thank you, Teresa. Thank you so much. This is awesome. Tracy's you Tracy
I'm sorry. I pinned the wrong person and like or in like that for that video because you were clipped in that video
I don't know you have to go to my wall and you you were in the
In the trip kick video. I don't know if you saw it yet, but you are in it. You are clipped
You are famous
Famous yeah, she's famed. I mean you run such a professional operation. Did you see that trip kick video?
What'd you think of it? No, man, I thought it was amazing. I thought it was a masterpiece
I thought it was sincerely just a work of art
He's probably having the beta one right or the crystal Marie, which one?
No, the first one you mentioned. Oh, yeah, okay. We're you know, be that was like alvira and all this kind of stuff
I know I used to
Oh, I right. Yes. I remember she had the biggest cities. Yeah. Yeah, she was hot. She was I will bang a virus
You know she's a lesbian now. Oh, she is
Well easy. Yeah, she's lesbian now
She's dating her like personal assistant for it was like, you know, she always had this like lesbian assistant
But now it's like she's like come out that it was actually her girlfriend the whole time
Hopefully those titties are taking are being well taken care of because they're beautiful. They're perfect. Yeah
perfect it is
But but yeah, so what's your favorite movie? We remember you. Oh, no, you told me you told me your favorite movie was the one
But they're very deep movie mentioned a very deep favorite movie. Yeah. Yeah, what's your favorite food?
favorite food
Crackers now
Fish tacos. Yeah. Yeah, kind of yeah, I like shot was a lot
Does your favorite out of every other food?
No, I like kind of like had I got my fill of them. I'm like not really like I'm kind of over fish tacos for now, but
Yeah, I mean, I think they're good. I mean I just like now I'm into McDonald's right now. I love eating McDonald's
Why that's not good. That's not good for you at all. It's tasty. It's really tasty
Okay, so let me ask you a question. Do you eat?
for
the
fulfilling your sense of taste or for nutrition I eat because I'm spending it hungry and I like and I
Stuffed myself and then
Then I'm like full for a while
Like I don't know. I drink I or sorry a to two double cheeseburgers the other day
That's like a lot of like that's like a pound of that McDonald's meat. That's like crazy to have your stomach and
It's horrible. I mean, it's good 80% McDonald's factory is known to have human meat
Yeah, but it's like 2% of the is foreign DNA, but that's probably in a lot of things
But okay, but again, you are you eating based on mouth pleasure or like satisfying your sense of taste or nutrition?
Are you subsistence? I like the taste of it. It's like and it's like it's just it's just like addicted plus
I get the coffees there they have coffee plus it's like walking distance and so there's all these
So you like a product of the system
Yeah
But I also eat subway and that's healthy right so it's pretty healthy and then I eat
Yeah, that's basically the two restaurants they go to. Oh, yeah the bagel store
And they're all within the same little shopping center. It's like across the street
So I love those places. They're so close
But I have to switch up, you know
I always use the apps too and the apps like you save a lot of money
So that's a that's a good way guys if you like on a budget like just use it
This is the app every time is you can get I think tomorrow guys is national burger day
I think it's national cheese and cheeseburger day or something and
We've done dumb as a country because we have national cheese burger day, I want to create national buckle that bullshit day
the
Okay, so for June 12th your birth year your day is okay international falafel day
World my day against child labor independence day
Where's independence day in Philippines? It's a peace day and
I guess national peace day. It's national loving day. It's oh, yeah
National jerky day national corn on the cob day
and world blood donor day
Well. Yeah. Hey, that's that's
that's that's that's that's that's
that's that's that's that's
Okay, so what is it makes his money mainly on the soft drinks because they have a deal
Okay, everybody's different here, but like what I've heard is that McDonald's is very much like a real estate company
Well, yeah, real estate. Yeah, the real estate is always a good investment
But I'm saying they make the money from having a deal with Coca-Cola that says they'll put Coca-Cola on their cups
And they'll get all free
Coca-Cola products and so all the drinks they sell are just pure profit
And so it's like that's why they like I really push selling like those extra value meals in the drinks box
So much, but let's also add imagine like that's a big franchise
so and I've heard that they buy the whole lot they wear a McDonald's gonna be placed there and
They they'll rent it out and that's like they rented out to the franchise see and that's where they make their money
I could be wrong because I don't know, but I'm not a fucking McDonald's expert in good things
Yeah, but you know whatever I'm an expert. I'm an expert. I'm big titty blondes. I just love
Oh, I love him so much like last night. What are you like Ann and Nicole Smith or who?
Yeah, she was hot, she was hot, but last night, like, last night, like, and I'm gonna see her again tomorrow.
I do just, it was a weird as night, crazy night, but I met a really, really fun girl.
Um, a pretty, like, she doesn't like it when I say, but like a pretty badass bitch.
And tomorrow we're gonna go to the art museum, like, trying to be normal sophisticated people.
Trying trying
Yeah
Well, hey, do you have a girlfriend yet or a wife like I don't know are you still are you interested?
Oh, I've never been married. I have no kids. I
Know I'm not late
No, I have dedicated my life to my duty. Have you talked to beat it lately? Yes. Yes. Yes
I sure have and I and I really really man. I hope that you guys can
Like I think there's a lot of
Love there
Yeah between me to you a hundred percent and it hurts me to you to
Hear some of the vendettas and I think that substance abuse is a little bit
influencing
They her behavior against you. I know you have not been by any means as antagonistic as she has been towards you
but
You know, I'm not one for compassion
But I guess that we're fucking friendship fucking happens, but I am gonna be compassionate to her and understand that sometimes
I'm trying to I'm trying to she thinks that like I'm like
Trying to hurt her or something like that by that. It's like we both they do the kind of the same thing where it's like we'll have
Just run our own shows like we wanted you and it's like I don't try to tell her how to run her show
She shouldn't tell me how to run my show like sometimes we
Were like in the same thing like the alcohol plays and I'm nobody speak right now because I'm drunk, but
I think alcohol really alters her behavior and she behaves in a way that is quite lashing.
It's a benefit, it's a balance, no not a balance, but it's going between anger and sadness, anger and sadness, anger and sadness.
And that anger has been channeled against you or I think that anybody that is going to be close to her
It's unfortunately gonna be the recipient of that
But it's not beta. It's the alcohol talking so like I remember I had a conversation with
wife of one of my best friends where I said like don't put it
On the I'm not gonna say his name. They say his name is Bob. Don't put it on Bob. Put it on the stress and
You get a creative you got to distinguish, you know
You almost got to learn to hear the stress talking and don't take it personal
So sometimes you have to hear the addiction
Talking and don't take it personal and that's what we're dealing with beta
And I think that if we do if we all do care about her we want to try to help her
Just not get deeper into this alcohol addiction because not it's not doing her any favors at all
Yeah, cuz it's like she's mad at the wrong people like you know, it's like
I have harm sure and suffer anybody who's close. She's gonna be mad at anybody who's close. Yeah
Just because you're there and and I think and then she is experiencing that emotion of anger
And she's gonna let it out and and whoever's available in that moment
Whoever crosses her mind in that moment
so
But at the same time I know that that that person has a good heart without a doubt and
And I they we
You know, I think that if we were to hopefully look back at this story
She can look back at us as people that cared about her and and
We're strong enough to not take all her
Offenses personal
Yes
Yeah, I know I'm gonna try not to think it personally, but she's like she's like
Oh, I'm she's like I'm she's like keeps wanting to like stay away from me and stuff
I'm like, you know, we don't have to like stay away from me. I don't want to have to stay away from her
I just I just like I think we should just be like normal and let's just be like accepting like, you know
We're even because we both like, you know, kind of like, you know
Go kind of like off and they do our own thing and like, you know, both independent
It's like I can't be like, you know, and like I like I love her
But it's like I can't I don't like to be told what to do and like, you know
It's like especially like running the show. It's like I've I've basically faced the consequences for if something goes wrong on the show
So it's like I'd like to be like, you know
Run it like I want to run it like well, I can look it so anyway, but she does give a lot of good advice
She has been you know, like she has looked out for me a lot. She's helped me a lot
And I don't like be mad at her about anything, but I'm not like I didn't do anything
I was like just like you know you didn't you were just there and and that's the problems that anybody who's just
Existing around that emotion that she's feeling at that moment is gonna be the recipient of it
and if that emotion is anger then
She's going to use that anger against you, whoever is around in that moment.
So it's a shame, but at the same time, and I think I've known Bida before, and I think
that this is how I look at it.
I think Bida has a very addictive personality and is fine, is genetic.
tightly connected which are the drinking and the streaming and
Those two things can be an addiction like streaming can be an addiction and
She is streaming and drinking and streaming and drinking and streaming and drinking
It's just not
Like I would do that and people were like oh yell at me and stuff like that
Like everyone's like but it's like now like she did like I she does it and then everyone tells me too
Like I don't ever just like I keep getting yellow. Well, I don't know like not as bad as like I was
But you gotta stop caring about what people say more people especially like these people the strangers in the chat
Like if you know how easy it is to manipulate human behavior
Via those chats. Yeah, yeah trawling and trawling and stuff. Yeah, yeah, so you get I know
You get it and don't look don't look so much outwards look inwards is what do you wish to?
accomplish what do you want to create and
Focus on that because there's gonna be a world of negativity around you just based on the context and we should operate
Unfortunately, I just feel it. I just feel it like more strongly than other people. I feel like the next like negative
You do and and I think that's what makes that a lot of people can appreciate you for that
But at the same time, there's gonna be a lot of people that are gonna not like you for that
But that's where that's where I see
You know an area in which you can improve on
Which is you gotta stop giving a fuck
About the people that don't like it. It's like no none of us none of us, especially when you're running a business
None of us are made out of sugar to be liked by everybody. Yeah
Like you find your niche, okay? You find your market segment and you find your niche
Yeah, and then you think the people that hate me. It's like a lot of people like hate me out like that
But you care about that does it fucking problem? I don't care
But it's like they'll chase away other people and then and then they're just like, you know just negative and that's like
I'm like, should I just start banning negative people?
You gotta have more of a fuck you attitude, dude.
If you want to be in business.
Dude, I can kick him out, but then I feel bad,
and I want to like, you know, like.
There you go, and I feel bad.
Well, don't be a fucking pussy.
Don't feel bad.
I just want to give people another chance
to say like, no, no, no.
Like you are, you want to be in business.
You better fucking distinguish.
It's like, I'm just going to be,
I'm not just going to be fucking.
John who's a very nice guy or I'm gonna be psyche awakens channel. Alright and psyche awakens channels
There's gonna be some rules and if you fucking break those rules then fuck you you're no longer welcome
And that's it and if you feel bad, you're not well equipped to run this
It is just like but I do like you know some people like just will flip on me and it's like at the last you know
It's like and then I like I'm like all trauma bonded and stuff to them
I don't know. It's like I'm a complicated person
but uh
I think hopefully be, you know, it's like I'll give you the space as long as she needs it, whatever
But it's like it's not it's like, you know people are just happy that when we're fighting and like some people like
Or a lot of people are happy and it's like so some people try to like exacerbate get in between us all the time
We were usually fine to talking one-on-one, but it's like, you know in front of other people
I don't know if it's like, you know
People does does the key work in front of other people
Yeah, because there's a show to be made out of that
Yeah, so I mean you you run I think that you you have a a lot of the proper intentions as far as how to run a business
but I
Asked myself
Is this the right business for this motherfucker to be in?
sincerely
Yeah, like like
I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I
Okay, but within I think you're I think you're receiving a lot of plus over enforcement
from people that their whole world is this
Little shit like just I think that if you want to run a real business
You you're not gonna do this bullshit
Like you know it's just dreaming is actually like I was able to like last month was a really good month for me
Actually, I made over like four four digits and stuff
Well, okay good. I'm happy. I'm happy. Thank you. Very happy. Thank you so much. I'm very very happy for you
Yeah, and you're crushing it like a real business. It's good. It's good. I
know a percentage of YouTube
Streamers are monetized
No, 3% and you're monetized. Mm-hmm. They're monetized. It's April
I'm very happy. That's good. Thank you. You put up you put up. I have no I'm good
Hey black RG, but black RG you miss when I played the blogger stuff
No, you know he brought up you he was like oh black RG was saying about Chris K
Like you know he's saying like you know he was trying to tell sake you got like he's like
But I want take you to meet him and then he's like then Chris K was on and it was really weird
I don't know if you saw any of that video, but
It's probably why all the pfp pics are old and doesn't cam up his worst even a lot worse worse even show in arm
He won't even show an arm. Who are you talking about? West? If you don't cycle off to do it. Oh, okay, rogue nomad are you uh
Did you have pfp pics? What does that mean?
Profile
Okay, your profile photo pics are old
That you in the picture is that like an AI avatar because I look at me
I have this angel like I like I like to think of myself as but like you know look look how like
Look how like Buffy is hold on to the moment in which I find myself trying to defend that is the moment where I lose they
This is reality. This is like this is this reality. I'm not gonna fucking
I don't give a fuck what these words on this chat say.
What do you think about this, Rogan?
Look.
Look, hold on.
See, like, look.
See a buff?
Oh, yeah, you look like a Greek god.
Don't look exactly like that.
Well, hold on.
Can I actually, like, I have a green screen behind me, actually.
Visual effects, green screen.
Green screen, okay, and so I see a screen. There we go. Hey, good job. Very nice. Thank you
Yes, yes, yes
It looks like you and McGregor pooping. Oh my gosh, well, let me see if I have a song I have a song for the chat. Let me see
There's two words that I don't need, I don't need to work with pride, I don't need to work with hate.
I'm not proud of anything.
What? What are you saying?
They're saying if I'm proud, like no, I'm not proud.
Like I simply hunt for my own weaknesses day after day.
I'm nothing, I'm not good at anything.
I just fucking hunt to try to suck less each day.
To try to suck what? Suck less each day?
Yeah, so classic so class what?
So close one at light. Oh, I try to just try to be a little bit
Not as weak as I was yesterday was just put it that way
Just trying to not be as weak as I was yesterday. I'm not proud of anything at all. I
Just figured out how to do how to make new layouts on my screen
Stay safe nice. That's some layout three. Oh, I can I can oh, that's why I was never able to do it
Yeah, I do suck I do suck and I like
Until the end of my life. I'm gonna try to suck a little bit less this day, but I do suck on
Well, you know Al Sir Crowley said he said I was born to suck
Okay
Do I have well, okay, I have a new commercial too, but you can see my trollopedia commercial. You see it hold on
Okay, one second me to set it into my repertoire
Oh, oh, I'm out of space. I need to delete something. Um, not that I'll delete
Shit I'm getting low on space
Oh, okay, I can leave this for now. Okay. Okay. One second. Okay, so this is a commercial
I made for my book. Tell me how you like it.
All right.
Okay.
It's gonna come up in this.
You know, this is starting to get in the world.
I think it's pretty cool, though. It's just taking forever.
Says the ultimate crime
Who's wonky boo?
Okay, uh
Just one second. I need to look at the chat says Alistair was a fake. Oh my god
He was actually very brilliant they docks they slander they gaslight they disrupt
But what if you had the ultimate guide to shut them down?
Introducing Trollopedia your field manual to decode expose and outsmart internet trolls
From classic tactics like love bombing to modern swarm attacks
Trollopedia breaks it all down. Know the playbook flip the script take back your power
Trollopedia
Yeah, yeah, damn dude that looks all fucking professional shit. Good job
So much. Yes, it looks great and that it looks really really good. Thank you
It's great. Yeah AI like the AI is gonna put like some marketing experts out of business because you just kind of does it itself
Well, yeah, but I mean it will like free up time for like
They're doing at the others part of the business, you know, because it's like there's a lot to a business
You know, it's very difficult. It's like, I
And it's very expensive like to hire marketing experts and they try to put you like a monthly fucking program
It's not like they listen motherfucker. I'll give you 5k. They get my business there
No, it's like no every month you're gonna have to pay this this and that for this many years
They what if I have enough clientele that I want to fucking get more clients
Yeah, but no, good job, dude. Badass. Thank you very much. Of course. Yeah. Yeah, he was he was bisexual before being bisexual was cool, right? Right, RG?
He was with thought it was loud. Yeah, okay. So did you want do you want a reading today because you know Teresa?
You know sponsored the panel and I yeah, yeah, I would love a reading. Okay. I agree. I'm excited. Thank you
Thank you. No problem. Okay, so this is oops. This is a really cool deck. It's called the
It's called
called the Gallery of Hallucinations Oracle.
It's supposed to be this old German 1920s art style.
Okay, first for you, we have the eye.
Okay, look at this eye card, eye card.
Is the eye on his hand also some maybe some some awareness that goes you know to other places in your body
Like you have some kind of like consciousness in your hand. Maybe but also like, you know, maybe you're being guided
By you know, yeah, you know, there's like the all-seeing eye. There's
You know, would you know where like waving comes from the origin of waving or shaking hands itself like that waving?
Yeah, what is that?
It means that you're not going to hurt that person that you're waving at.
Oh yeah, that's smiling too, it says I'm not threatening, but it means I'm threatened by you.
If you had a rock even and you could, you're kind of showing an empty hand by waving and you're not throwing a spear,
you say, and then if we evolve here to North America, a shaking of hands means that I'm not drawing on you,
Look at this one. This is called the harvest. This is next to the harvest. Okay. I've been working on something. It's going to be paying off. I don't know if it has to do with a woman or something like that.
Oh, thank you. Yes. I 100% am. Thank you so much.
Okay. There's some women's heads. So I don't know if there's a woman or a girlfriend. This one says the watchtower. There's another eye. More eye symbolism.
The watchtower also looks, reminds me kind of like between a woman's legs a little bit. I don't know. But you might be, you might be like doing something. I don't know. I just...
I just think about, yeah, the watch tower.
I think there's somebody watching you also,
or somebody watching everybody.
They're also, maybe you're on watch or something.
Okay, but yeah.
I am because of my work, I'm closely watched,
which is okay.
Okay.
I just want to remember,
I don't know if you're good morning somebody,
this is remembered as a woman with some flowers
and she's either remembering the flowers or-
I am, like, remember, I don't know if you were,
but last week I lost a friend and teammate.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Well, I see that, I see that, you're just remembering and celebrating the thing, also
another one reflecting, like thinking about...
some things, also maybe thinking about that person a lot,
remembering, reflecting all next to each other,
but also we had that earlier card with this one right here,
this, the watch tower, which is also like the water,
also reflecting a little bit in the water on the bottom.
Yeah.
Well, a lot of reflection, you know,
a lot of what you learn from that person that you lost
and trying to incorporate into your everyday life
to hopefully honor them by sharing all the lessons
that would learn from them.
Okay, finally we have the ghost lore and we have necromancer. Okay, so these come together like this ghost lore and this necromancer
It's almost like
There's some kind of like story or it's like some kind of like from the like from the dead is like bringing a message to you somehow
Also, like you know chanting over a book
I would think a little bit like these three women chanting over a book some kind
I always just think that some kind of magics involved
There's a four-some
Yeah, yeah, I'd be a four-some. That's you. That's you the book is actually you with your legs open
Bitches three hot bitches and we're having
which is a beast with your the Jack Nicholson
Yeah
You have a dry ass if you wish I'd love that's capricorn. Yeah capricorn usually you're reading
Okay, easy. Do you want to come up on panel and get the reading?
Uh, what about smiley face killer? Oh, yeah. I've never seen a woman's vagina. I don't know. It's a
Yeah, I had an ex and she was kind of had a weird shape of vagina, but
I didn't like really look at it. I just touched it
He's touched it like like it was a thing, you know, I just approached it and I touched it and then I walked away
Yes, I like
Tim and Lee walked up to it actually then it exploded into like a to like a fire hydrant, you know gusher and then like
Well, that's what a lot of people they don't get about squirters. Hey, you got I actually like I was surprised how much how much liquid came out
But then I now I heard that it's pee, right?
It's hot the first time
But then actually that when you date one and you you have sheets in your fucking bed and you have to change the fucking sheets
I only have enough fucking sheets because they so I stole it
I thought they she had to start bringing her own towels and shit
They they I'm not gonna be buying new sheets every fucking time she squirts
Because I don't want to sleep on that shit. Hey, it was wet
It was it was wet and I can't sleep on that so every time that you just have sex to chill fucking squirt
And then all of a sudden I say, oh
Hey, I just want to go to sleep and then now we have to change the whole fucking sheets
So it's like it's sexy in theory, but then in practice you're like, okay. They I want to go to sleep, bitch
and this fucking bed is soaked so this is not enjoyable anymore
easy you know i'm reading i easily i'm sorry easy oh i got you reading later okay i'm sorry
how did i get reading um yeah yeah thank you very much for my reading i really appreciate
i don't know why it keeps coming up
But when I see a picture from last night
Okay, I'm gonna exit and then unless I can just change it here. I don't know well as long as there's not like, you know
How much of your penis is showing?
Do you wanna see mr. Bigpipes?
No, I see mr. Bigpipes, um, um bulge
No
Night, I rather not but how can I change my profile picture you can you think go off stage and then change it
And then you can come back. I'll let you back on. Okay
Mmm, sorry, it was a suit. I'm in roll guys. It's a little bit chewy and it's I have like look
I'm gonna like lift the fucking frosty off of it, too
Little bit too sweet, you know, it's a too sweet and then I taste like the plastic from the
Oh
It's too sweet
You know why can't a buck in bagel place get the cream cheese frosting right it's like it tastes like a hello
Who is it?
Is it paid for?
Yolanda is it paid for? No, okay. No, I didn't order it. I'm sorry
Pizza for Jolanda
Yeah, but I didn't order anything I
Think might be a prank
Okay, yeah, it might be a prank
Hopefully you get to keep it. Have a good day
Can you just can someone please fucking pay for the pizza, please? Oh, I'm sorry
I would have I supposed to let you back up and someone pay for the pizza, please like don't stop sending me not paid for pizzas
It's so rude. You pay for the fucking manure. Why can't you pay for the pizza?
Okay, you're getting it backwards. How about you like
Send pre pre paid pizza and not paid for manure and so they don't need the manure. How about that?
How about that?
Is that an idea?
Anyway, it's someone from Louisiana, New Orleans.
They're lucky I don't talk to their number,
but I'm not gonna play as dirty as them.
But it was, I did give them area code earlier
and it was like a New Orleans number.
So anybody know someone from New Orleans?
Probably Black RG's from New Orleans too.
Probably him doing it or something. Who's Yolanda? I don't know. I don't know Yolanda
Oh, actually, there is like a Yolanda in the chat, but I don't think it's you know, I'm sure it's not
Yolanda or maybe is that yeah, because uh
Rogue nomads big thing was like Walnatisa or something or like malatisa or waltisa
Let me look at my uh, how long I've been on
I don't know. Oh, let me see. Okay
Okay, I'm kidding my link
I'm sorry, I pitched you too loud guys that kind of gross, okay
Well, no one's gonna talk, okay, yeah, oh, okay.
I don't know, so let me see if I have something to show you.
Yeah, video file, okay.
Oh look, I got some blogger clips.
I thought I had some blogger clips
There's scum
Attractable at the fuck my blogger stuff
I don't go about color go by personality
Summer you said like 20 minutes ago. It's fine
Yeah a couple days ago
I didn't say it's 20 minutes ago. You just did yes, you did. Okay, whatever. We're not gonna do a whole ghost thing over here
Well, that's what you want to do. We need stage
We just got staged
that
I
Look at that
Like they sleep so comfy. Look at that. Where's that? What's that kiddie's name?
Her name is baby girl
Baby, you're paid for baby
Is it paid for is it paid for
No, that's it's it's a prank. It's a prank. I'm sorry. I didn't order anything
Yeah, yeah
Do the vlogger happier lives than not
Fixed cats also outlived non-fixed cats. Yeah, but Marcy that's because there's there are more hazards outside
There are you know
Other animals like I had a cat that got eaten by coyote
unfortunately
or coyotes
There's other dangers. There's cars. I've got a I've got a cat get hit by a car, but they also
cats like I let I open the door the cats go outside
They roll around in the sun they just start rolling this it's a cat
They're almost like they're on cat and then they like to go climb trees be in the bushes
You know they like that little do little play. I mean, you can have it making a perfectly good lives indoors
I have like, you know, and especially this in the city, you know when you're in a building like a apartment building
You know that works, but I have a bunch of cats and I have a nice backyard
There's a lot of area a lot of trees. There's a lot of nature
They like to they like to go out and play and they like to do their business outside and bury it and stuff
so
Bob Barker was a pioneer in oh, yeah, have your cats spayed or neutered. I'm Bob Barker
Have your cat spayed or neutered
Was it I
Didn't order anything cats and dogs. Yeah, I didn't order anything
Control the pet population. Have your cat have your pet spayed or neutered
Who just said it my mom. No, I don't think so. It's a prank
Why would my mom send me food would not paid for I don't understand. No, okay, sorry
Yeah, very weird
Yeah
You should get a life. I mean, it's like what they're gonna waste pizza people's time
How did they find your address?
Because I think because when I got
copyright struck, you know, it's like
He got my address during that process
Or he maybe got it from Alexander McQueen.
That's another option.
Oh yeah, here's Blogger. Here's Blogger thing.
Made fun of myself a lot and I was able to like take a lot of criticism.
And so...
I think sometimes when you don't when you're not able to do that people are more targeted. You're you're more targeted
Well, no, I do make fun of my I've told every embarrassing story about myself
I like I put myself up at like let I let all the trolls say whatever they want
You know most like having less their doxie or something. I am very I'm very I'm very self-depreciating
People like to see like humility and all that, you know, even if they're not humble themselves. They like to see people
be humble and he'd like show you melody. I agree, I agree. I agree with what he's saying.
Wow, because I like myself. I need to humble myself. Okay, Joker. I mean, okay, what's your
name? Blogger. Oh my gosh, blogger is such a megalomania, Napoleon complex.
Okay, once again, I'm gonna pull up a minute clip I think that I think that that human being is suffering and I think that
You know we shouldn't judge him for his suffering who blogger. Yeah
He's suffering. He was saying that everyone that watches everyone. That's on my panel is retarded. Well, so do you wouldn't agree with that? Would you?
Yeah, I know exactly
Who is this person?
Whenever you want, just let me know, okay?
It can be the day, it can be the day.
But you would have to ask me, can I please have a reading?
Because it's like, I don't, just like...
I don't have forced readings on people.
Some people don't like readings and some people are against it for religious or ethical purposes
of their own mind and stuff like that.
So you would have to ask me when you want it and then, you know, but of course you're
here on the panel.
So it's like, if you say, may I have a piece of a reading, I have a question, I'd like
a few cards.
i'd be happy to read for you okay so you asked me like a reading well you get
when you ask me that you would like to come on the panel you can type your question in chat or
say general because you're your member so you get a you get a free reading um and anybody any member
yeah there's a there's a few people that i'm not i'm gonna have them i'm just like i got this idea
from saman and uh and i think they beat it if they want to come back on the panel i'll get to be
I mean, it's like, 25 for a month, we can have like,
but you, I mean, but you have to understand that some of these people have bigger problems.
Like salmon has a bigger problem than you.
I know.
So you got to adjust your rates.
No, but I'm having a high rate.
I'm going to have a high rate.
No, no, but you can, you cannot just mimic the rate of somebody who has a higher.
No, I'm not doing my own I'm doing I don't I don't remember his rate. I'm just doing my own thing
I'm just doing my own thing and that's gonna be I decided like I was first I was like telling them
Yeah, I'll look you know, I'll bring you back for like
20 bucks then like he kept kept he kept like saying he would and then he didn't so I'd earn isn't 25 bucks
And I liked the $25 figure and the fake copy Alex should be a 50
But I was giving him half off last night now he'll be 50 now if Alex wants to come back it's 50 Alex, okay?
Okay, because we have to put up with you screaming and being annoying and
Breaking to us and stuff like that. You've already like on so many of my videos got taken down to limited
Monetization because of your big mouth
Alex and saying like did he hear like that person that person time in the chat got a
minimization tattoo all over their back yeah I got a who's tattoo yeah that person time
like they got a minimization tattoo like they got minimization tattooed on their back
minimization tattoo yeah I don't think I'm so happy I'm so happy for them yeah they got
this is really bad ass work like they how good they got minimization on their back it's pretty
Got people triggered shout out to me. Yeah, well, I have a I've added a cool Smith on my back
Yeah
He's kind of he's curious. Yeah at the
Yeah, there's like dying good that tattoo and I asked myself like what is the logic behind the tattoo?
It makes no sense, but I mean, I'm not gonna be one to judge
But that that person time God many men's and tattooed on their back fucking blow. I don't I would like that
I thought I heard someone at the door, okay, nevermind.
Um, yeah.
I mean, they said-
The thing of all that food, all that food,
what is going to happen to that food?
The food?
I think, hopefully they get to eat it,
but they might like provide, I wish they would just-
What if they're on a diet?
Like, what if they didn't want to eat that trash?
They'd probably just throw it away or something,
or take it back to the restaurant.
Oh no, see, that's not good, that's not good.
Yeah.
Oh, that was a little kitty, kitty, kitty, cat.
This is Lola.
Oh, hello, little baby Lola.
Hello
Yeah, she's adorable look at she looks so happy and safe
You're happy over there little baby Lola I
Send her I sent her five pets three of them on her little head and two of them on her little belly. Oh
What are you doing care?
You know last night Lenore brought in a mouse, and it was like squeaky
Isn't that picture who's that woman in that picture is that your girlfriend or some?
You went out last night
She's a squirter
Is that you sure? Yeah, it is me. Oh
What?
That's me very attractive
But
Well, she was a world of fun last night. Have you ever had a couple pick you up?
Dude last night. That's what they fucking did. This is so crazy. There was a couple. Where's the guy?
Yeah, there was a fucking couple. They closed the bar, okay?
So 2 a.m. came around and they closed the bar and these fucking people are just like, hey, you guys want to go here, Bob?
And like this chick and I were just fucking drunk as fuck. So we're like fuck it. Let's go
So we went and then did the guy watch you guys or did he?
No, no nothing happened. They wanted to play beer pong and stuff. So at the end of the day
I was texting her now. We were like they what the fuck was the point of that?
They what would they invite us they what the fuck would they just randomly pick us up and invite us
but they just want to play beer pong and drink and and they bought all the drinks this mother
fucking made a really good prime rib like i don't get like they just they we did you selected us
and they hey you guys want to come over that's sure we went but there was nothing sexual at all
it was just like beer pong and and and steak did he did he suck your dick no he didn't suck my dick
you wake up the next morning like you know under the on top of the ping-pong table or yeah
I woke up on top of the ping-pong table with it with a sore ass
Oh, no, what the fuck happened? I think what the fuck think what what where?
What something must have happened? I think they
Where am I where am I? What's going on here? No, motherfucker. Of course that didn't happen
But they but what did happen is that they were just like hey you guys want to come on and we did go
and then it was just like it was beer pong and shit and you know it's so fucking
stupid because the beer pong they just had like water in the cups I'm like why
are we doing this I thought it'd be a beer pong is supposed to get you fucked
up is they why you have water and stupid ass cups there's some fucking Mormon
party or something the fuck is this but we ended up getting home like at 7 a.m.
each of us and then I am still drunk and I just kept drinking and that probably
And I don't know where tonight will take me. I know I'm not gonna see her tonight
They I got I have a client that gifted me some tickets for fancy as art shows that tomorrow
I said hey you want to go to an art show? I'll pay for everything, but thankfully they
Is all to go
We're gonna pick me up
Well, I will take you I will take you take me. I'll take it to the art show. Yeah, 100% 100%
And what are we gonna do afterwards?
You want to eat something you want to get something to eat? Yes
All right, then we can get something
Okay, they
It's not a date. It's like two motherfucking friends hanging out
If you look at me improperly if you touch me properly, I want to put a bullet through fucking school
Well, you know, I've told you this I've told you this
What did you just say me nothing?
Not I've ever told you this psyche and like but that's why you gotta respect my boundaries, right? I respect yours
Well, I mean
Yeah, we can go to our show. We can go get some of it. All right, and that's that good friends. They friends do
Good friends. Yeah
100% okay
Well, do you want to see something really cool? Let me see. Hold on. Yeah
Why don't we go to the matrix?
Hold on, let's do the matrix thing.
Well, this is like the matrix, more green, more green.
I think this works one second.
I don't know if this will work.
I'm just trying something new.
Right, here we go, okay.
So, try this file.
Where's it?
Desktop?
Come on.
What do I save it to?
Downloads.
Okay, nevermind.
Can't figure it out. Well, anyway
I got a new computer like recently so it's like, you know, what kind of computer do you get? Yeah, I got a mini PC
It's like a small, but it's like a little mini gaming PC, but it's like really
Yeah, it's really cool. What brand is it what brand it's called
Hmm, let me look at it. It's called
I'd like to try.
G-com, G-E-E-K-O-M.
G-com.
G-E-E-C-U-M?
K-O-M.
G-com.
Like, G-E-E-C-U-M.
K-O-M.
G-com.
G-com, yeah.
Okay. Nice. I have an MSI.
I have an MSI gaming laptop.
I think...
I mean, but I barely use that motherfucker.
I think I turned that on.
I'm not a big fan of being in front of screens.
I'm talking to you on my phone,
but I think if you work in front of the screen
and you're a man, then you're kind of a fucking pussy.
Then you gotta work with your fucking hands.
They actually, they think the mouse,
you have to click it and stuff, that's your hand.
smart smart yeah I stand corrected mr. Watch this here watch this let me see
if this works home so be so cool if it works dry as a theory actually this might
not actually oh yeah this will work this work let's see it's gonna be the
matrix once again all right okay here we go
They're working. I guess it's not working. Oh look look there it is
How's that?
That's bad. Oh, we're in the matrix. Yeah
damn
Perfect that works
That's pretty cool, huh? Yes. That is very very very very cool
They really like one one one zero zero zero one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one one
I I don't remember the last time I was that challenge in life
Objective-based programming with iPhone. Oh my fucking god. That shit was fucking now. You don't even have to like learn
I mean now it's like the AI just writes it
And that's the interesting thing about AI is that technically it can heal itself, right?
so they'd say like there's a problem within the code the syntax and
The AI itself can go into the syntax
Fix it and move onward. So little by little is just like where we yeah, but we're kind of putting their fucking they were as the human
factor
The human is like human created this super complex
Syntax to the point where human is no longer a part of it
Know well, it's like well, but that's the scary part is like eventually what if they don't decide we don't need humans anymore to like
Notifix them they have they figure out it fix themselves and stuff and the humans are just like you know
These like kind of dumb apes to them because they have they have all the intelligence
That's but at the same time is like that is what is one aspect of nature
Like that is just the human is just one fucking species of nature and it's so egotistical
to think that you just
Can rule the whole fucking
Florence honor
When you're just one little aspect of nature and then you can create this fucking being AI
But there's you know, there's there's there's a lot of animals
they that that need to survive and
What is AI gonna fucking think of animals?
Hello, nature itself like I just
Yo
Hey, good afternoon kind of dry
What's going on everyone?
How are you?
Not too bad. Just hanging in the shop
What kind of shot
Clothing store. Oh
Very. Oh, that's really cool. Very cool
Oh, in Canada, huh?
Yeah, I'm parked on the coast right now.
Nice.
I remember when I was in Europe, like I learned,
at least in Holland, it is much,
it doesn't require as much money to dress very well.
Like you can get really nice clothes for, you know,
by no means what they will cost here in the US.
So like being stylish is not as expensive,
you know, like parts of the world as it is in the US.
True
Where'd you been Canada dry? Oh
Fuck man. I just been busy moving
I haven't seen you for a while
No, it's been a couple months. Yeah, Christine and I had a falling out. Oh
Don't worry about that. That's what she does. She falls out and then I was on summer's show
And then she started kicking me off the panel three times or she kicked me off three times for ten minutes each time
So someone made 30 bucks off me, so that's fine now.
That's Christine's game.
Yeah, but Christine's all, she turned on me
because Crystal was saying that she was murdering
like, you know, minors and stuff like that,
and it was just like.
How's it going guys?
She was just ridiculous to me, and so I just like.
Not too bad.
That's wild psyche.
Yeah.
People are trying to buy clothing.
I just got a couple of customers.
It's all good.
I'm sorry, I didn't I thought you're talking to the chat. No, you were talking to the customer cool if you get customers
Yeah, I just like pretend like we're not here. Yeah, we're not here
Oh my god
Well, you're eclipsed in some of my on some of my shorts and I wouldn't click in my shorts. Yeah
I clipped this show with you in it and so you're in a bunch of clips.
I don't know, I should play one. Let's see if I have a classic Canada dry clip.
Let's see, video file. Okay, here we go. Let me see. Classic Canada dry. Let's see.
How do you hold thumbs up?
Oops, let me see. Downloads.
Desktop.
you know what I have to go actually to my shorts but not my actual shorts my
shorts on YouTube let's see because we have some classic Canada dry moments you
know and it's like because you were here at the beginning of the show
oh Elise is on okay my channel okay here's the shorts okay so let's see
Canada dry where are you oh here you are
And descend with it with gross lessons, and you know fuck I test myself all the time
You need to speak these cards up, and I'm like oh, I can do it. No, I've come in a car back
I can see it three times what happened with Paige. She hasn't been around at all
And here and this is the clears too, right? And I just make sure that it's solidary because fucking this shit is crazy
It is absolutely crazy. So I suppressed my spiritual awakening with medication and still do. Yeah
Yeah, absolutely
I don't take medication I smoke weed and you know, I I think I was about six years ago
I started experiencing pretty severe megalomania and
Basically like whether I was listening to Drake or watching a YouTube video or a commercial would pop up
I was like
Everything was ticking with something. I had either thought about was thinking about. Yeah, everything started making sense way too much
Yeah, to a point that it started to
I started being like what's going on. Yeah, and I went to talk to a doctor
Yeah, about it and I got
I just take a basically like a lexapro, like a pretty standard anti-anxiety med to this
current day and I've learned to transmute and there is, that's why science and the
spirit, the theory are two different things, but when they work together there's no reason
why that can't be harmonious at some point to you or emulsify in your beliefs and yourself
and you know you can be crazy and fucking psychic like you can be you can be a scientist and still be
you know a bit of a psychic or an intuitive and everybody is intuitive we have that in us naturally
and you said it's a matter of what we nourish or what we do recognize and that we do build on so when I was young
there was definitely something wrong with me. I didn't have anyone to help me with these things.
So I just kind of figured it out on my own. You know, that's information, knowledge,
falling down rabbit holes, finding outlets, finding people who are like me. So I didn't
feel so fucking alone and weird. And then I didn't need to go in a straight jacket.
I mean, it's all based up so easily fucking influenced. I used to be a very
King Vaughn going and rapping about killing people and I used to be a very
There were a lot of moments and I still have it with my friends where it's like again
I'm not gonna claim
That I'm psychic because I don't know how to use it. However, that's why you're here
I can
I have a lot of synchronicity in thoughts and in things I do with the outside world
that I can't necessarily predict, but it happens, so like...
that do you know what I mean like I don't know how to channel it and be like I know that
right because you know tomorrow but it but then something I said will or yeah hmm
uh say to you create will you speak you manifest your thoughts and project to
distract what you feel right for the most part well so it's skeptical a little bit
I had someone on reddit tell me that they thought that I was someone who is tuned in
and that I was having an awakening
Who's there? Oh
What are we watching? No, we were just watching some shorts. Hello
Yeah, I was a reruns. There we go. Can I dress here? Can I drag Audi? Who can in a drive? Oh, no, I don't know this guy
Hey, what's up, man? Who's got?
He's he's uh he's gone. I'm god asshole. Yeah
Where were you I thought you died no dude, I just been doing shit working traveling
Oh, I lost 50 bucks then. I bet 50 bucks you died. Oh shit
You heard Michael died Canada dry, yeah, I was there for that
Yeah, he died again
The butterfly so I think he's okay. That's awesome, man
You can only die twice now. He's no resurrect. Nobody's resurrected Michael
I just thought that he was resurrected by my bed, you know, his girlfriend thanked me when uh, when he was gone
Yeah, oh
Thank God
She said it
Mirinda did not say it like that. She doesn't think God he's gone
She's
No westwood. Nobody wonders why I'm wearing 500
It kills him. What if Mirna kills him? That's what I think happened
She didn't like what was going on between you and him. I think
They were a couple yeah, I'm not gonna be embarrassed by this guy. He's killed that like he's tarot
Yeah, sure that you know what like fuck this guy. I'm gonna kill it
She was a fatty so she probably sat on oh come on come on come on. Don't see all right listen
Listen, I'm gonna go then before I get
No, no, let's see what he did see what he did. It's okay see the shirt I made sick
What does it say? I'd rather to see you out of a shirt, Canada.
It's got a mermaid on it.
A little mermaid.
A little mermaid is my favorite movie.
My favorite Disney movie, at least.
Are both of you gay? I know. Why don't we use gay? Is there one gay, too?
Canada is gay. I'm bisexual.
Oh, really? Canada is gay? Okay, well, that makes sense.
I'm just kidding. I saw one with a woman once.
I think they were just holding hands, but...
It is. I am gay.
He has a shirt that says I'm not gay, but my boyfriend is
Meow meow meow. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just playing
And right you're gay you gay
Michael Michael Michael
So, how did that guy die? I
Have no idea. I have no
Specifics were disclosed
Well, I would make fun of myself a lot and I was able to like take a lot of criticism. Okay, and so
That's one dumb blogger. Okay, so who else is here? Oh, lima 13 hold on one second
I don't know who this is, so let's put up the banner here.
Hello.
Hey, what's good, what's good?
How are you?
Hello, hi, hello, hi.
Who is this?
Lima.
Lima?
What are you doing?
Are you Hispanic?
He's a bean.
Watch out, because it could be Lima Delta.
Yeah.
What is that?
I'm new here, I'm new.
Is this Carl?
Is this a beat his friend Carl?
I'm right. Hello
Is it a freeze? Hello?
Can you hear me? Yeah, is this Carl?
See what this Carl this guy has no idea what you're talking about. Okay, Carl
You should like disguise your voice better and it's like you're not I mean it's kind of like obvious. I'm sorry
Oh, maybe I'm just like really good at I don't think that's like no, I think it's a random ass person
Okay, who are okay to tell us about yourself Lima. Are you from Peru?
Yeah, you got it. You got it right. Yeah the room the TPP
Yeah, why are all the TPP people coming here?
TPP, yeah
Coming here and like
Acting up on my show. Yeah, I've gone there
Tell you to do that or it's like you just all come on your own or something. How do you find out about my show?
No, you're being interrogated motherfucker
You know, you're a good guy, I think you might be a good guy, but I'm just wondering because we have, like, you know, some assholes, like, yeah, let's see, it's the state-turned guy and, like, the LES, that guy's an asshole.
You know, Hot Mess Summer and Christine?
Uh, Christine, yes, I've talked to Christine, and I've talked to Summer, yes, I've talked to...
Christine's a mortal enemy. Did she, Christine, send you over here? Did she harass me?
Uh, no, bro. I mean, sorry for calling you, bro. We don't know each other. You don't know me. I don't know you guys.
Are you going, bro? Hey, but, you know, have you, do you know why Christine's mad at me?
I had no idea.
I don't know anything about it.
She doesn't know on the internet.
She would rather deal with people on the internet
and the drama she has there
than take care of her grandchildren
or be a mother to her son.
The internet's more important for her.
Let me see.
I've encountered people like that.
I'm not going to say that I have the same concept of her as what you just mentioned.
Well, guys, watch this, it hasn't happened to me.
This is like, this is what happened.
This is like a little Crystal Marie and myself here.
Chris Panna gang that stalks you?
Well, he was in the white, that white courtesy gang that did hurt me that was trying to kill me.
I guess she she's like a lot of criminal record and she's trying to cover it up. So
We're just gonna break it
Like when she was a nurse and she supposedly did
Come on, you know some people are like really mean and that's gonna be okay
And you know like that first thing I told you
The same people or
Like you wouldn't even believe that they're age, you know what I mean? It's like
Take over 100 years old
Well, the Hawaiians are doing like buy one get one fifty percent. I wouldn't understand that a bitch
That would act like that like that is like I guess she she's like a lot of criminal record
And she's trying to cover it up. So
We're just gonna break it
Yeah, yeah, yeah, she's got a big criminal record she's got to get fucked
Aaron got friends
No, no, no. Yeah
Why what you do?
She was a see-a-cramel?
Yeah, she was a bad criminal.
What'd she do?
She killed kids.
Oh my God!
Well, she puts them in, um, they put them in these sex trafficking rings, and her bro and her friend probably fucking are unpart of it.
And we're gonna get them all fucking caught real quick.
Yeah, they're not trying to help people, they're trying to get people fucking caught up.
That's it.
Christine does this?
Yeah
Why do you think that she says that she's a part that she works for?
fucking listen
she says
that she is
What's it called, you know first aid what do you want?
And she also says that that she's
I don't think she's she said she's just security or at the mall the weekend right now yeah she said that or is that what she told you she said she works with Alex at the mall Alex Alexander the thing
Yeah, I'm just looking along
Saying it's more security. You're the same lady. But yeah, so she's she's false and security so she can
Do other bad things with other parts of law. So yeah, she's fought
I'm having a hard time believing it right no, she's going to jail forever
I wouldn't really mind going to Jeff Reaver if it was me, because I'd finally get like a city's five sex three showers, you know.
Oh, but it's not a bad guy.
Yeah, but you're not a bad guy, and you would like Excel because you're like a man.
But don't you?
I don't think I see a tag in each other though.
She's like, look at her way over there.
You guys are all going to try anything off you that use the system, you know, that say that they're doing like companies and like, did you grab a button up bro?
Yeah, I can do those one for.
And they say that they getting this people houses and they don't.
And they got like, they're giving a difference in so many money because.
Uh, yeah, you know, this is all fucking false and that fucking bitch is about to go down and she's about to have no job
They're all doing bad, you know, it's it's about it's an all-system
It's a bad system that's about to go down from Georgia to
There to Florida
What are they going to do?
Well, they're about to get them to go to prison.
Is that going to happen soon or this year?
What do you think?
I don't know how that works.
Who's going to go first, Epstein or Christine?
Christine.
Christine, I love you.
100%.
I wish Christine was here.
Well, because she did bad stuff online and it's it's caught up to her
Because you can't pay people you can't pay people people to abuse you people. That's against the law
Yeah, that's a long this is consensual right unless I say I want yeah, so and when it's on video and it's yeah
It's against a lot when it's been by five people
Yeah, and on different networks, we are not even the same fucking people so who is so who has a video of pristine
Because we're not all the same
Well, we couldn't out because it's it's her work. It's what she did
It's out of her it's out of her her her own
Device Christina, I really hope that out of her own device. You know what you mean device, you know
People do bad things under their own device
Yes
So, you hacked Christine. Well, that's illegal too.
No, man, I never, I would never know if you fucking hacked her to do bad things to me.
And super, like, heavy.
Well, you're seeing I need you years ago years ago. I got this years ago
I don't even know I got all her shit years ago
I told you this I told you this I tried to tell you this this is why I did not want the fucking
Fagotry I said when when I seen the thing with
Then I knew the gods and you don't even know what I knew
Well, no, they have like they
You know they're friends with people that aren't friends with us and you know like criminals
Yeah
Ladies and gentlemen, Limp Bizkit and Snoop Dogg.
Freak baby, freak freak baby, freak baby, freak freak baby.
Red light, green light.
You ready to roll?
Tell me when you're ready to go.
Tell me when you're ready to roll?
Red light, green light.
Tell me when you're ready to go
I got the keys baby
Put your mind at ease baby
Go player, lay in the cheese baby
I know you're fighting, fighting my steeds baby
But I came, came to please baby
Don't wait, lay the grease baby
Don't play, play, shake the knees baby
Your fellas mad at me baby
Oh well, enemies baby
Who's bragging, they ragging on me baby
Who's breath
Drag it on baby
My friend I'm about to go to at least some chatter bait with that guy. Thank you. We're gonna suck each other
Did you hear Chris K is gonna once to come over and masturbate with me?
Not just be
I don't like that. I shouldn't do that. He said he had $1000 in cash. He wants to come over
Well, I would say don't do that because he was one of the ones who was
Like to bring it to say gang that had like a lot of money to marry
Okay
I
Yeah, he came over the night and he's like hey like money talks. He's like how does everyone want to see the second?
I do a chatter
Yeah, it sounds cool
Do be very where I watch him fighting with a black dwarf and the black dwarf
I'm not kidding you see that
You thought a dork in Las Vegas and he lost
Well, I've seen something else where he tried to act like he was a cop. Yeah
Yeah
It's terrible. I'm sorry. I mean interrupt. Yeah
When he did that that meant
He's worthy of death. Oh my oh, well, it's like I think he's just ignorant. Maybe you know, it's like yeah, but that's pretty ignorant
pretty ignorant
But I mean, we're all we're all gonna, you know, pass away some
raw human beings, but no, we're all we're all
I'm saying he he deserves it
Hopefully maybe he can change his ways that'd be good. You live in two people changing their ways
I don't you don't okay, so it's Chris can a game that stocks you
Well, he was in the white that white courtesy game that didn't hurt me that was trying to kill me
You know, aren't you without you're like a part of spanish or something and they don't like it's been it
That's kind of weird. Oh
No, I wasn't in he was in a game that is against me
Why were they against you though?
They were trying to kill me, uh
They didn't was jar jar stinks is backing you up and they're all saying yes, they did
Why would they want to do that? I don't do they want to kill me. Do you think or unalive me?
Well at that time
People were saying that I was married to a black guy, which I was never married engage anything to a black guy
You're married to Sam and I don't know I would love to be married to it's black. Oh my gosh. Look how bad. I look
You're beautiful. I
Should put makeup on you look fine
Just got a filter put out a filter on the camera. I will put on makeup for you
No, I'm not doing that.
I don't like to sit there and like I like to be like Al Bundy with my hands off and then I like to unbutton them.
Like just like this, you know what I mean?
Put your hands down in your other regions.
Oh my god.
Be careful Chris, I don't want to get in trouble.
No.
No, but what I'm saying is that these people are being very mean. Oh my gosh. I look terrible
See, this is why I don't want to be on air
I make you look like this
Now you're beautiful you're beautiful
Thank you. Thank you. I really great stomach. Yeah, I do too. Look at mine. Let me see mine
I don't know if I want to show mine.
How does that look?
It's good?
Great.
Thank you.
Okay, I want to take off the, okay, yeah, you can show yours.
Well, I don't know, I don't know, I got, like, oh, guys.
I'm like a non-baggy band.
Okay.
Do you have a hole in your jeans?
It looks like there's a little hole in your jeans.
There.
Okay.
That looks like mine.
Really twins. Hold on. I'll put myself back on.
Guys, let's compare.
Is it good?
No, I'm fat dude. I'm fat. I'm a bloated dude. I just ate six cookies. I feel fat too
I just had McDonald's and Big Mac
And I will say to you
Won't have to worry about me. You might have to worry
about your family from
their
family trees
That's what I said. You might have to worry
When you say shit about me, you might have to worry about
Crystal yeah, you get the job
Okay, I have to
Oh, my God, chat, CPT, addiction, commercials are coming up.
Hey, Lima, are you here?
I'm back.
Lima.
Hey, hey, hey, can you hear me?
Hey, did you watch that?
How was that?
Yeah, yeah
You know Christine was involved in and I'm just kidding. She was she's not involved in it
I'm sure Crystal Crystal said she was joking by the way guys and it's like Christine was like Christine thought I was like
I seriously believed it and was like saying that she was involved in it. No
No, no, I never thought I'd never for one second that I believe it up for one second
But now
So it's such a bi tch to me
I'm starting to believe Chris
You're having a YouTube feud something like that
Well, I I don't know. I just believe Chris because I'm mad at Christine
Okay, I know I know she didn't have anything to do with it
But she she paid $30 this summer to kick me off the panel three times
so I couldn't even like get one word out and then
And then she told like it was like we're gonna kick me out of beat his chat and stuff
Yeah, I know it's nasty, but it's like what can I say besides it was like you know for it. It was a joke
Well, I thought it was a joke
And she she took it the wrong way that's what you think
Well, I didn't do anything Crystal Marie said everything. It's just like but it's like yeah, it's my panel
But it's like I wanted to hear these
The wild theories is but the same thing it's talking about. Oh, I saw Bigfoot in the woods
It's like just like some ramblings of a of an insane person. I mean Crystal Marie is fine
I mean, it's like I hope she does like if she needs help she gets help but but she is like, you know
Seriously, she's always with the conspiracy stuff and I like conspiracies and I don't know how much is like, you know
I don't want to like
I don't know if someone has a serious mental illness. I don't want to like keep
No, Christina's like said fuck you. She said fuck you's like you should go to hell
She's like kicking me off of summer's panel and stuff
mm-hmm
There's not slander. It's not slander because it's like people are allowed to tell their stories, but it's like I
Was like I was taking it as like joke and plus she didn't use any last name or anything. It could have been some other person, right?
As I see what you're saying, but at the same time I would add like as I was here and you asked me
Hey, you from TPP like basically you said you didn't say the exact words
But you basically ask are you here to fuck with me, right?
Yeah, that was kind of like what I I'm just
How you call it? Yeah, I'm just saying what I felt and I think that's what you meant
Yeah, right. You are you look a lot of people are here for that reason
You you asked me the question in a straight up answer in my answer is no
I'm not here to fuck with you. My point is that
Sometimes people take sides
And they, they, they, I mean,
no one ever takes my side.
Like, well, some like a few people sometimes do,
but it's like a lot of people don't.
And then it's like, then I always get like yell that.
And it was because people,
as my friends are harping on me,
the girls will harp on me about this stuff.
So it's like, it's all, it sounded like slander.
Well, I did say several times, it's not true.
I mean it sounds it sounded to me like a like an insane person like the ramblings of a crazy person plus
I didn't hear any last name. I didn't really hear she said she didn't even say nurse
She said medical person or something like that or she's she said
She said first aid person so
But they're a team, but it's like, yeah, it's like,
there's not teams.
It's like, it's like, and it's like, not actually,
it's like, not our relationships,
our personal relationships are not nobody else's business.
It's like, everyone thinks that they have a right
to say something about my first relationship
with somebody else when it's like, you know,
worry about your own relationships.
It's like, you know, it's like, I,
it's really not your business, like me and Vita
or me and Christine, it's like, you know,
I'll talk about these things sometimes, but it's like,
you know, it's like, not for you, not for anybody else besides us to work out, you know, it's like, so it's like,
people just stop, can stop trying to like, tell me what to do about it and stuff.
But we have to be honest and realize that sometimes it's aligned on the sun.
Right
I said I thought I was just ridiculous. I mean people have said much more outrageous stuff in the store
This is the show that's a and I get to say the horrible things about it
Like people doesn't should be used to the panel versus this stuff said all it does is leads a more conversation and clicks
It doesn't read no one ever gets arrested usually unless there was actually some kind of crime
It's like it's not like, you know, she's being harassed by the FBI or something like that. I'm trying to make her
mad? No, I was just trying to show Malima because she knows about it. I can show you some other
clips of Christine like when she's actually talking to Crystal and Crystal's accusing her of like
abusing like, you know, there's other stuff that it's like, I think it's outrageous, but Crystal's,
but she laughed it off then. So it's like, you know, and she, Crystal sounded crazy. So I don't
understand if Crystal sounded crazy. And she was laughing at the allegations. And so I think she
Like this like beat it doesn't want me to play clips or of her but then she doesn't care
Tripp kick does and she's like she's like well I love Tripp so she don't you don't love me
Like I can't clips with you even my own it's like I don't know it's weird
Uh
Well
Just how would I feel?
Well, how would how would you feel if you got if you got kicked off the show three times for because of christian?
Because christian didn't say anything to you to go to hell f you and she's another chance saying stuff to you
What was she saying in like uh in uh
in the chat on Sunday, you know,
when she went over to Alexander's chat.
I know she was talking in the chat and I was like saying,
I apologize and everything,
but what can I do more than apologize, you know?
But she's gonna like take it on.
Like, all these women that I've gotten invited with
are so unforgiving.
It's like, guys, I can like, you know,
it's like talk to guys, these women are like,
some of these women that like, you know,
Emma and it's like, they're...
Can we agree that...
I mean, we all have emotions, but can we agree that?
Yeah, I'm not just cold.
I always have the door open.
I have the door open.
Are a little bit more emotional?
I think women are more emotional.
Men are more emotional, because women
are the emotional ninjas.
Women feel emotions stronger, so they're better at handling it.
I think the emotional men usually are in jail or dead
already.
Well emotional men like usually if they're emotional they sometimes if they have empathy and so like you know
They wouldn't be necessarily be in jail because like a lot of people in jail have a lack of empathy, right?
and so and you are and you and you are
According to the emotions you feel at the moment and you make a mistake, right?
and my emotions are like different because it's like I kind of like
Um, I have like the I have like the world conscience instead of this is my own private my personal conscience
It's like the world. It's like I feel like every so it's like so I'm very detached emotionally because it's like it's too much
To take everybody's emotions at once because I'm so sensitive to so I like don't feel I try to like detach emotionally
Like so I am like an alien in a lot of ways like I do feel like
Like a very like just clinical like and like so you know you numb yourself sometimes to
No, I am myself. I'm an alien. I feel like I'm like, you know, I am myself. But yeah, I'm like,
I can just detach myself from emotion because sometimes logic has to rule and stuff, right?
It's like, but I can like, you know, sometimes you can't help emotion. You can't help logic either.
So it's like, but I have a balance in both. How do you, how do you feel?
I understand what you're saying in
My personal view is that, men usually use logic and they'll contrast their feelings with the logic
and they'll go according to that, and that's why I previously said that the men that are emotional and don't...
They use logic and they just act on emotions, they're either dead or in jail, I think.
And I'm not from, I'm not from the, you mean the, the, what are we, the noble Castro.
You mean the, like the Salvador, you mean like the group, the...
criminal group? Is that what you're implying? Novel Castro? Is that the question?
Are you a gang member from El Salvador? That's what I'm trying to understand. Is that the question?
I don't know. I don't know. I didn't ask that.
MS. MS. That's what he's asking.
Novel Castro is Latino, I believe.
Yeah. Yeah.
You suck. I sound like one. All right. Well, no, no, no, I'm not I'm not affiliated with
With MS. Oh my god. No, I'm not. I
Am not not at all my brother. I'm a saint. I never been I never broke a law in my life
And I don't I don't break the law
And trying to get all Mexican gangs with me and say what I'm trying to I'm trying to unite with all the like
You know the Hispanic gangs no matter where they're from
You are or noble. Yeah, I am
You are I already have to I have J-Dog and and and
Plumsy bean gang on my team. So I just need another
Well, I'm not, I'm sorry, I can't help with that.
I can help with translation maybe sometimes, but that's about it.
Okay, yeah, you can translate it, but it's not a good model, it's not a good model.
Yeah.
Okay.
Ignorance is bliss.
Reference is ecstasy.
Yes.
Yeah, the cocoa leaves are amazing.
Definitely, they're the best.
I say, some people say that
the culture in Peru and this and the food
and Machu Picchu and this and that.
Do they do those ayahuasca ceremonies where you're from?
Where I'm from yeah, yeah, they do it usually in the jungle
But I personally I haven't done it myself, but I know people travel all the way here to do it
And yeah, ignore disabilities. Yeah, do you remember? Well, yes. Yes
I talked about coca leaves and how coca leaves are well coca
It's the best thing
That's Peru's best product for the world for sure
He said you like cock
Cocoa leaves. Oh coca leaves. Oh, okay. Yeah, is that like I'm is that like a chocolate?
No, we're talking about
Oh
No, we're not talking about that. We're talking about the leaf
That's what they use it for right like to like, you know, maybe no became out of right
You're correct. Yes
They process it and they make
The little thingy thing. Yeah, like noble said that's no that Peruvian snow
Well, who's who's importing all this into the country?
That's a good question. You want me to give you my conspiracy theory?
Yes, please.
I believe that since Peru, Bolivia and Colombia are the main ones,
because it naturally grows here in this area.
As a Peruvian, I would say that Peruvian is the best, but I mean to each his own, but
At the same time who controls here, I think in my
World view how I see it who controls everything here is the states
The the army the Navy that they all come here to train the guys here
And so I believe that they're the ones who control how much goes out
In where it goes and how it goes. Yeah
Well, so but yeah, but you don't know anything about it, right? I
Don't I don't know I don't know nothing and the only thing I know is that I don't know. Yeah, I
Don't even know what I don't know
Yeah, I really don't but look look how about this you like this style? Hold on
Like that
That's great, bro. That looks like I'm
Without the woman. It's like a mushroom trip kind of I mean I generated that art. Yeah, it's pretty cool. It's cool
Yeah, so um, so you never you you have you ever
seen
Cocoa leaves like the actual plant
No, but I've seen a lot of cock
Okay, no, I really haven't well except that one time in the prison shower. No, I mean the jail shower. I'm just kidding
Well
People like before chemistry and all of that and people making the snow
Before all of that
People being used in the the leaves like they chew them. They just put them on the side of their mouth to make it their mouth numb
Definitely. Yeah, but it's like
Have you ever done the snow?
Yeah, I'm done some okay, so I
would say
It's if that's a hundred percent
The the the feet the feeling that you get when you chew the leaves. I would say it's a five
five percent maybe ten
It's like a car
Like it's a helmet like what do you mean five like a five and ten percent strength or what?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying like the effects and the
the side effects also like
Like I said comparing to what you've tried if that's a hundred
The leaves will give you like 5% or 10% so you can be all day chewing that shit and you'll like
You'll not be hungry and you'll be working all day
So like I said before people be using it like
Forever in in this area for that and it's kind of like a sacred
It's part of ceremonies also. Yeah
It's like I know like a lot of plants are sacred and I think there's like right there's like shamans that
Kind of like well, you know guide people through these psychedelic things and people like will see like a lot of
You know, like like they're angels and all kind of I know the trips last a lot longer there than they do
Like it's smoking it like DMC or something like that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, but these are serotonin inhibitor and so it's like it will last a lot longer when they do like the the mixture
but
Yeah, I've never done it like that. I've only done it only done it like that, you know the powdery
I've had it in the vape. It was very very strong, but it's like it's you know, he's not trash
It's it's like oh, it's like it can be really good
But you have to get it in one of those vaporizers and like a like a like the where you know, and then take it from a vape
It's really good
Okay, I can make it but it's kind of frustrating to make and it's like because sometimes you don't
Yield very much out of it. It's pretty expensive to get the bark, but it's legal in the US
That's amazing. That's super good. Yeah, it's like the the fact that we as
humans
We've banned some plants and make them illegal
it's it's
Oh, yeah, that's absolutely. I mean stupid as fuck, but well
Yeah, that's that's who we are as a society
That's that's why I always say
Bruce should legalize
Coke in
I mean the plant the plant is legal here, but
Talking about the snow
We should legalize that and sell it to everybody
Pro would be rich if we do that
Yeah
Yeah, Nick
What up Nick
Nick is all the way out there
Nick is chewing some leaves, I think
No, but yeah, definitely you should
If you can get your hands on some coca leaves, you should
you should have a Kava have you heard of Kava I know that's like there's like you know there's
something that's like there's like a stimulant that they do in ceremonies and it's like
it's kind of like a more legal I don't know have you heard of that Kava like a tea out of it so
I think I heard of it but I'm not sure of what it is
I've heard of this, kind of like, they do it in ceremonies also with the ayahuasca.
They basically blow, I think it's tobacco, I think, they blow it up to, I mean, in your nose.
They put like a straw on your nose.
And on the tip of it there, it's like a lot of tobacco and they just blow it inside of your like your nostrils and like
I don't remember the name of it
But um
Yeah, I mean what I heard about ayahuasca is that because ayahuasca is a drink
Yeah, okay, and
One of it's a mix between like basically two plants one of them. It's got the DMT and
And but if you just drink that your stomach is going to just
The enzymes on your stomach are gonna just eliminate the DMT so you're not gonna trip
Well, like RG said, he has some, wait, you're going to want one for the, for GMT, it's something called mimosa, how still is?
Yes, yes, so that's, but when they ask the shamans, like, I mean, how do you know, how did you know
how to mix this one with that one so you, you can, like, you can trip? And their answer is
the plants told us.
Yeah, interesting. Yeah, well that there's like animal spirit or animal and plant spirits very big in
certain
Yeah, I would say
That there's there is a lot of truth to that and a universal medicine kind of thing like there's pharmacokia in Greece and
Modern pharmaceutical, but it's kind of like a it's scary and just but pharmacokia is basically which crap
Which is basically a pharmacology, right? It's like just like using drugs and in certain words and vibrations and all kind of
Interesting the empty for mimosa. It's mimosa. How still is or you know, I can't see a cost. Yeah has like a high percent
I think those are the highest percentage on
Tree barks, but I think the highest is the mimosa, but it's it's it's legal
You can get it like on the internet
for like
50 bucks
Wow, this Rachel. It's on sale a little bit for twenty five percent off like
There's a guy, I think it's called Mimosa Hestilis Rupark or something.com or something like that.
You can look up how to make it too, but it's all, it's like, actually like I would just like
find somebody else. It's like, it's like, if it doesn't work, it's like, I'm like really bad at
doing things exact. Like I always screw up like perfect, but I think they're exact.
Like, and so it's, you need to be very exact for it. Like, you know, so I've had like some,
not excessive festival pulls of it, but I've done it.
I don't know. It's just like it feels like kind of a waste when I do it. So I don't know. I'm not that great at making it
Hostiles oh hostilists. Yeah, okay guys
I'm gonna end this stream because I want to get the clips made of this dream
But I'm gonna come right back on in a little bit. So I'll see you in a little bit
Okay, thank you and yeah come back. Thank you very much and then I think yeah
We want to spawn anyone's response to the next panel. Oh, there's Nick. That'd be be awesome. Okay, so I'll play this song out
I've been missing in my sleep
eating steak somewhere in the middle they both take a break
he'd trade his knife stick for a fishing pole
chase her laughter like it's his patrol old page
don't you know you're the catch of the day and this cop's got one hell of a line to say